animeblogger.net 2016-05-08

# AnimeBlogger.net » Privacy Policy

January 28th, 2009 by Maestro

    Privacy Policy for AnimeBlogger.net and blogs hosted with AnimeBlogger.net 
    (hereinafter AnimeBlogger.net)
    
    The privacy of our visitors to AnimeBlogger.net is important to us. 
    
    At AnimeBlogger.net, we recognize that privacy of your personal information 
    is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we 
    receive and collect when you use visit AnimeBlogger.net, and how we safeguard 
    your information.  We never sell your personal information to third parties.
    
    LOG FILES
    
    As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log 
    files.  The information in the log files include  your IP (internet protocol) 
    address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the 
    browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), 
    the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site.
    
    COOKIES AND WEB BEACONS
    
    We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when 
    you visit our site.  This could include only showing you a particular ad once 
    in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as the 
    forums and Antenna.
    
    We also use third party advertisements on AnimeBlogger.net to support our site.  
    Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons 
    when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such 
    as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP 
    address, your ISP, the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, 
    whether you have Flash installed.  This is generally used for geotargeting 
    purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) 
    or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking 
    ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).
    
    You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party 
    cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such 
    as Norton Internet Security.  However, this can affect how you are able to 
    interact with our site as well as other websites.  This could include the 
    inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or 
    accounts.
